
export const quizQuestions_2 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the primary purpose of controlled components in React?',
      choices: ['To simplify form validation', 'To handle form submission', 'To manage form state in React component', 'To create dynamic forms'],
      correctAnswer: 'To manage form state in React component',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, what is the onChange event used for in form elements?',
      choices: ['Submitting the form', 'Handling keyboard input', 'Tracking changes in form elements', 'Resetting the form'],
      correctAnswer: 'Tracking changes in form elements',
    },
    {
      question: 'How can you prevent the default form submission behavior in React?',
      choices: ['Using event.preventDefault()', 'Setting onSubmit to null', 'Using formNoSubmit attribute', 'Changing form method to "GET"'],
      correctAnswer: 'Using event.preventDefault()',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which hook is commonly used for handling form state in React functional components?',
      choices: ['useEffect', 'useState', 'useForm', 'useFormState'],
      correctAnswer: 'useState',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the value attribute in a controlled input in React?',
      choices: ['To set the initial value of the input', 'To determine the input type', 'To disable the input field', 'To set the placeholder text'],
      correctAnswer: 'To set the initial value of the input',
    },
    {
      question: 'What method is used for submitting a form in React?',
      choices: ['submitForm()', 'sendForm()', 'handleFormSubmit()', 'onSubmit()'],
      correctAnswer: 'onSubmit()',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, how can you handle the submission of a form without a form element?',
      choices: ['Using a button click event', 'Using a link click event', 'Using the onFormSubmit attribute', 'It is not possible'],
      correctAnswer: 'Using a button click event',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which React component property is used to associate a form element with its corresponding state?',
      choices: ['data-state', 'state-key', 'state', 'value'],
      correctAnswer: 'value',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the htmlFor attribute in a label element?',
      choices: ['To define the form element type', 'To create a reference to a form element', 'To associate a label with a form element', 'To hide the label text'],
      correctAnswer: 'To associate a label with a form element',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method is used for resetting the form fields in React?',
      choices: ['resetForm()', 'clearForm()', 'handleFormReset()', 'onReset()'],
      correctAnswer: 'onReset()',
    },
  ],
}